CARLOS MARTÍNEZ

FULL STACK JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER

CONTACT

linkedin: https://linkedin.com/in/coxato

github: https://github.com/coxato

website: https://<u>coxato.dev</u>

SKILLS

JavaScript

React.js
React Native
Redux
Next.js
Node.js
Express.js
MongoDB
Firebase
Python
MySQL

PORTFOLIO

Git & github

https://coxato.dev

ABOUT

Full stack JavaScript programmer with more than 3 years of experience building modern web applications. I work mostly with the MERN stack (MongoDB, Express, React, Node), I also have knowledge of React Native, firebase, python, git & github, etc. I always give my best and I am willing to learn whatever it takes.

Take a look at my work or get in touch! https://coxato.dev

EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER

ASX asx.mx | Feb 2020 - Jul 2020

- Build modern web apps with React.js and Firebase
- Making React Native apps
- Teamwork with graphic designer to implement corporate identity on websites
- Build admin dashboards.

FREELANCE DEVELOPER

Self Employed | Jan 2019 - present

- Build websites for freelance jobs
- Make scripts for WordPress plugins
- React Native apps

WEB DEVELOPER

libraryaudio.com | Apr 2021 - Jun 2021

- Build frontend for libraryaudio.com
- Make scripts for WordPress plugins
- Work with a lot of audio files and making custom players
- Teamwork with graphic designer to implement corporate identity on websites

EDUCATION

FULL STACK JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER

Platzi | 2018 - 2020

Platzi is an online school for learn software development, graphic design and marketing, in this school I took the "JavaScript School career" where they teach the entire JavaScript ecosystem (frontend and backend)

you can see my platzi profile https://platzi.com/@cems/